But before that, let's go to the next
one!
Then challenge live broadcast!
That's my main job.
Have you ever thought about live
streaming?
I often watch sports programs.
It's a must for sports programs.
The biggest difference from reading
script is that there is no script in
live streaming.
This is good for people who are not
good at reading script.
You don't have to follow it with your
eyes.
You can say what you like.
But you have to express your feelings
while watching something.
You need to bring the words in your
head quickly.
You need to be fast.
You said that you can read the script
slowly.
But you need to be fast when you read
the script.
When you see something, you should
bring the best word.
If you don't have the best word, you
should bring the closest word, better.
We have two videos.
I will show you.
This is the video of the one-man live
that was held at the Saitama Super Arena
on August 23, last year.
I will show you the video.
Next we will show you these trifecta of
idols.
Let's see!
Chow circuit.
Now, the forest car race is about to
begin.
There are no customers.
Saitama Super Arena has started.
Now, Sakai will go from inside.
Sakai goes first.
Sakai is in the lead.
And Tsujino from the outside.
Sakai and Tsujino.
This is a one-on-one situation.
Anne is late.
How about it?
Tsujino. Anne is late.
You're late.
Now, one-on-one.
Tsujino and Sakai's one-on-one.
How about the first one?
Is this Sakai or Tsujino?
It's a close game.
Anne is trying to reach the goal.
She is the only one behind.
She is trying to reach the goal.
She is clapping.
She is clapping from a place where no
one is.
She is the last one behind.
How about it?
Wow!
It's like watching a TV show.
You're late.
That's it.
I want you to do this.
What?
I've never done this.
So, please look at the picture and
choose the appropriate words.
Make the final decision following the
viewer's participation.
This program is a program where 6
people who are active to promote
something exciting
challenge various things and raise the
excitement barometer in the world.
Thank you for watching.
First, I'd like the three of us to do
it.
Sakai, Koizumi, and Yurushika.
Let's start with Sakai.
I'll do my best.
Sakai's commentary start!
Now, the obstacle relay is about to
start.
Ah! It's started!
It seems that Hyurin is leading.
I thought Koizumi-san was a little
behind, but...
Oh!
Next is the cardboard...
The cardboard roll relay has started!
Ah! Hyurin is struggling to get in.
Ah! She's been torn apart, but what
will happen?
Ah! Tsudaaki-san started first, but...
Oharu is behind, but...
Oh! They collided!
Hyurin and Aki-chan collided!
What will happen in this battle?
Ah, the three of them are cute today...
Ah!
Next is the big ball rolling relay!
What will happen?
Oh! Tsuda-san is overwhelmingly
leading, but...
Where are the other two?
Koizumi-san is catching up to Hyurin.
Oh!
Next is the balloon inflating battle.
Will Tsuda-san be able to break it
quickly because he was first?
Yoshikawa-san's way of inflating is
pretty good.
It's stable.
Koizumi-san is a little behind, so it's
going to take a long time.
Her hair is also quite messy.
Oh! Tsuda-san and Yoshikawa-san are
about the same...
Ah! Tsuda-san broke it first!
Tsuda-san is the goal!
Next is the battle between Koizumi-san
and Yoshikawa-san.
Oh! Which one will break first?
Oh! Yoshikawa-san broke it first!
So...
Yes! Yoshikawa-san is the goal!
So, the first place is Aki-chan, and
the second place is Hyurin-san!
It was a good result!
Thank you!
Please give it to Sakai-san!
Now, here is Sakai-san's live
commentary judgment!
Oh!
Great!
It's interesting!
She explained the game properly in her
head.
She told me that there is such a game.
She said, like, it's cute today, too.
I was saying that.
It's really good to put that in.
And she said that she messed up her
hair.
I can see that.
I can see her hard work.
That description is very good.
I was surprised at the high quality!
Sakai-san passed the live commentary!
Yay! Thank you!
It's amazing!
Thank you.
Next, Koizumi-san, please challenge!
I'll do my best!
Yes!
How would Koizumi skating be
Let's get started!
The three-person race is about to
start.
Sakai is leading.
Good luck to all three.
Tsujino is also.
Where is An-san?
An-san!
An-san is a little behind.
An-san, good luck.
An-san's smile is the strongest.
Tsujino and Sakai, which one will win?
Tsujino leads in the near car.
He made a goal.
An-san is pushed by Tamarin and is
heading to the goal.
Tamarin is also cheering for An-san
with a good smile.
Tamarin's support is hot.
He will soon reach the goal.
An-san, good luck.
An-san is soon...
An-san just reached the goal.
Thank you for the great performance!
I tend to stretch my neck.
I'm glad I felt it myself.
Now, this is Koizumi's commentary
technique.
It's here.
It's amazing.
It was amazing.
It's good.
There was a proper explanation of the
game, and then the situation.
Who is in the lead and who is behind.
There was also a part where I was
cheering on the way.
That was a little good.
At the end, Tsujima and Sakai were
lined up.
They said,
And Publin.
I didn't know at all.
I didn't know the name, so I couldn't
say it.
I know that, so I said the name
properly.
I explained the situation.
I think this was well conveyed.
It's wonderful.
I have to say that word instantly.
It's hard.
I can't say it.
But you're much better than reading the
manuscript.
Ah, I see.
Now, let's have Yoshikawa-san for the
last.
Thank you.
But, you're good at it.
I'm better at it.
Let's start Yoshikawa's commentary.
Yoshikawa Hyo is in the second half.
What will happen in this game?
The three of them are cute today.
The three of them will start the race.
Start!
The first one to start is Sakai.
Anne is a little late.
Tamarin is coming out.
It's a fierce battle.
Anne's smile is cute.
Sakai is spreading her legs.
It's a good feeling.
She just finished.
Pamulin is leading Anne.
It's been 20 years since the race
started.
I can see two people in the back.
Anne finished.
Congratulations.
The three of them were impressed by the
hot battle.
Thank you very much.
Congratulations.
I'm scared.
I'm glad.
Let's start Yoshikawa's commentary.
Eh?
I could see that you were very excited.
But it's not a comment that you're too
excited.
I want you to look at it with a certain
degree of anxiety and proceed calmly.
The worst thing was that you didn't say
who was the first one.
You said that Anne was the last one to
reach the goal.
One, two, Tsujino, Sakai, which one, it
was a close game.
You didn't say that those two had
reached the goal.
You were very excited.
I was excited.
You should have held back your
excitement a little more.
It was a commentary of the best of the
best.
It was easy, but you all did it.
How was it?
It's difficult to say the words
instantly.
And I was a little surprised at how
little I knew the words.
I was able to say it because the video
changed while I was saying it.
You forgot about the previous one and
had to go to the next one.
This is also a feature of commentary.
That's all for today.
uld have popular I a
I will show you the demonstration and
application of the game.
It is normal to show the movement of a
sports.
I will show you the game that does not
move.
For example, there is a small square
table in front of me.
A water bottle is on it.
It is said that 90% of the human body
is made of water.
I will show you the movement of the
water bottle.
If you can do this, you will be a
successful person.
No one has done it yet.
For example, you can do anything with a
water bottle.
Please tell me the date.
How many days is it?
It is around March.
March 31st is the date.
It is the day before April 1st.
On April 1st, 1982, the final of the
MSG League was held at Kuramae National
Stadium.
It is the day before that.
At first, the first pitch of Antonio
Inoki and Andrew the Giant was decided.
Antonio Inoki injured his leg and was
urgently discharged.
There, Killer Curren's appearance as a
diamond was decided.
In other words, this March 31st is the
day after the announcement of the
appearance of the diamond.
It is the day that Killer Curren
arrived at the bedside while making a
throbbing sound.
I don't know, but if you say a lot,
it's amazing.
This is it.
If you say something like this,
I see.
What?
I think you didn't know what you were
saying at all.
Killer turn.
I see.
I would like you to challenge everyone
like that.
Then, let's have the three people who
didn't do it earlier challenge.
Let's start with Tsuruno.
Yes.
Please subscribe to my channel!
Ah, then I'll take this one.
I'll take one more.
Yes, you chose one.
Well then, Ms. Sujino, please do a
30-second live broadcast.
Yes, today I would like to introduce
this live photo of the 7th issue.
I will pick up one of them.
Ta-da!
This is number 265!
It's over here.
This is Hitoka Sakai of Tokimeki Red!
How do you like this sparkling smile?
People who see this smile will
definitely be excited!
Hitoka Sakai's photo book will be
released on February 28th!
You will definitely fall in love!
Thank you!
I was promoting it.
That's it.
Let's judge Tsujino's comment.
It's over!
It's different when you speak with your
own words.
I don't have to read it with my eyes.
I could feel that you wanted to convey
the goodness of Sakai.
If you say more about the contents of
the photo, it will be even better.
It's surprisingly 30 seconds.
It's a good feeling.
You don't have time to think.
You should go on.
I think it was good.
Next, let's see An's comment.
What will you choose?
I'll choose a nice shirt.
Let's start the live stream of An-san.
Start!
Everyone, the T-shirt I'm wearing is a
goods T-shirt of Super Tokimeki Channel.
There are six cute girls here.
This is an illustration of the members
of Super Tokimeki Channel.
And this looks pretty flashy, right?
But that's not true.
It's a nice T-shirt that you can wear
casually.
This T-shirt has a hidden story.
This T-shirt is the T-shirt I wore in
my birthday party in January this year.
I'm wearing this T-shirt in the live
photo.
So when this T-shirt is released, it's
a spoiler.
Everyone, surprised!
Wow!
It's a spoiler.
Please sit down.
Let's get started.
This is the live stream of An-san.
This is the evaluation of An-san's live
stream.
I'm glad you read the manuscript.
It was like TV shopping.
Certainly.
I know it's highly recommended, but I'd
like you to spread it more from this
T-shirt.
I wish you could say more about the
shape and so on.
It's strange.
I'm glad you read it.
It's not like a manuscript.
Let's have Suda-san for the last.
Good luck!
What do you want to do?
I want to go with hair accessories.
The time limit is 30 seconds.
Start the live broadcast of Suda-san!
Hello everyone!
First of all, please look at this
colorful hair accessory!
This hair accessory is a hair accessory
of the costume of Ennis.
Everyone has a flower motif, and it has
matching beads.
If you wear this, you will feel happy.
I'm yellow, so I always wear this and
I'm a friend of the live broadcast.
This is my friend!
Everyone, please make a makeup and wear
it!
This is the evaluation of Suda-san's
comment.
It was a good 30 seconds.
Did you draw it in detail?
I drew it with a pencil.
It was full of feelings you wanted to
see.
Overall, it was a TV shopping, but I
could see that you wanted to convey the
goodness.
I also put in a lot of things like how
to use it and how to use it, not just
the shape.
I'm glad that there was originality in
that area.
The point when you broadcast is to say
the sentence as short as possible.
I'm in Shibuya right now.
There are a lot of people.
It's sunny.
The sky is very blue.
The blue sky is spreading.
It's easy to understand that it's
short.
I came to Shibuya, but there are a lot
of people.
If you say that the sky is very blue,
it's a long sentence.
Instead, let's say it in a short
sentence.
Suda-san, you did it.
I passed!
So, this time we have a guest, Kiyoma
Shiguchi from FreeAnimals.
He will be our voice actor.
What do you think, Kiyoma-san?
Well, I think you guys aren't suited to
read scripts.
You should do it freely.
I see.
We started this project with KageNare,
but you should do it freely.
Without any script.
KageNare is also free.
Without any script, you can do it
freely.
I see.
You should keep in mind that you should
read the script.
I think it's better to do it freely.
I see.
Please follow my lead.
Yes!
We will do our best!
Thank you very much!
Thank you!
See you next week!
If you like today's narration,
if you like the live streaming of our
song,
if you like our hair style,
if you want to see our daily life,
if you want to try narration,
if you want to see our next live
performance,
please like and subscribe to our
channel!
Leave comments too!
Bye bye!
Now I can do it, even if it's tears
When I'm lost, I remember right away
Even if it rains, I'll smile
Look, let's go anywhere
Goodbye, goodbye, to me of yesterday
The city after the rain is sparkling
My heart is like a sunny day, the sound
of the puddle of water
I'll play the rainbow piano
Goodbye, goodbye, to me of yesterday
The city after the rain is sparkling
My heart is like a sunny day, the sound
of the puddle of water
I'll wear a rainbow dress